# Mário Antônio A. Rodeghiero

#### FRONT END · DEVELOPER

88034-102, Rod. Amaro Antônio Vieira 2259 Apt. 404, Florianópolis - SC, Brazil

🛮 (+55) 99691-2866 | 🗷 mario.rodeghiero@gmail.com | 🎢 www.mrodeghiero.com | 🖸 mariorodeghiero | 🛅 mariorodeghiero

### **Summary**\_

After a solid career of 10 years in the telecommunications area, I decided to change the area and look for new challenges. My free time to study development, contribute to Open Source projects and improve my English. Graduate student in Data science and Big Data Analytics and in parallel I continue my studies focused on Front End, I have as main programming language "Javascript" but I also have knowledge of Python and I love ReactJS. I keep my personal codes and projects on Github and I have also developed my blog to put my learning into practice by publishing articles on development. I am also the creator of "Vue Theme", theme with more than 44900 Installs in the Visual Studio Code editor.

### Work Experience

Claro - América Móvil

Florianópolis - Brazil

DATA CENTER ANALYST II

Jul 2014 - Jun 2017

- My responsibility as an Analyst II was to be responsible for managing all routers in the cluster Florianópolis SC Brazil and developing applications to guarantee the company's SLA.
- I created two programs using Javascript, Python, Sheel Script, HTML and CSS to monitor all network equipment and to test DNS name server
  resolution.
- Reducing the response time to incidents by 50% and avoiding that none of the 80 equipment went unnoticed after analyst configuration activity.

Claro - América Móvil Florianópolis - Brazil

DATA CENTER ANALYST I

Apr 2013 - Jul 2014

Responsible for deploying and managing the Data Center infrastructure in high availability and mission-critical environments such as Oracle Solaris servers DHCP, DNS, TFTP, LDAP, Cisco and Huawei routers, Switches (Cisco) and CMTS (Cisco, Arris, CasaSystem and Motorola), responsible for the generation and distribution of DOCSIS (Broadband Internet, VOIP and Video On Demand) technology services to more than 170,000 customers in the cities of Florianópolis, São José and Palhoça. Key activities include managing LAN and WAN routing (IPv4, IPv6, and NAT), BGP and OSPF, traffic balancing control, link management, monitoring, troubleshooting, network documentation, and support level 2 for operations in the state of Santa Catarina - Brazil, assisting, guiding and planning demands for Datacenter teams.

Claro - América Móvil Florianópolis - Brazil

TECHNICIAN III Aug 2012 to Apr 2013

NET - América Móvil Florianópolis - Brazil

TECHNICIAN II Jun 2010 - Jul 2012

**RCtel Solution in Telecommunications** 

Florianópolis - Brazil

Support Analyst Aug 2008 - May 2010

#### Education

University Estácio de Sá

Florianópolis, Brazil

GRADUATE STUDIES DATA SCIENCE AND BIG DATA ANALYTICS

Dec. 2018 - PRESENT

University Estácio de Sá

Florianópolis, Brazil

TECHNICIAN'S LICENSE COMPUTER NETWORKS

Dec. 2016

### Technical skills

ReactJS, Javascript, ES6, Python, HTML, CSS, SASS (Preprocessor), styled-components, ElectronJS, Bootstrap, Git/Github, Webpack.

## Languages\_

Portuguese (fluent), English (intermediate)